Fear what's inside.
Annihilation is a science fiction, horror film directed by Alex Garland.
A biologist signs up for a dangerous, secret expedition into a
mysterious zone where the laws of nature don't apply.
Lena, played by Natalie Portman.
Dr Ventress, played by Jennifer Jason Leigh.
Anya Thorensen, played by Gina Rodriguez.
Josie Radek, played by Tessa Thompson.
Cass Sheppard, played by Tuva Novotny.
Kane, played by Oscar Isaac.
Annihilation is a 2018 science fiction cosmic horror film written and directed by
Alex Garland, loosely based on the 2014 novel by Jeff VanderMeer.
It stars Natalie Portman, Jennifer Jason Leigh, Gina Rodriguez,
Tessa Thompson, Tuva Novotny, and Oscar Isaac.
The story follows a group of scientists who enter the Shimmer, a mysterious
quarantined zone of mutating plants and animals caused by an alien presence.
The movie is a co-production between the United Kingdom and the United States.
Released theatrically in the United States by Paramount Pictures on February 23, 2018, Annihilation
was released digitally by Netflix in a number of other countries on March 12, 2018.
It received largely positive reviews from critics
and grossed $43 million worldwide.
According to Empire magazine, the film addresses "depression,
grief, and the human propensity for self-destruction."
The film explores themes of depression, florida,
quarantine, coma, based on novel or book.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.